[

    {
        "product_id":1,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Baby Yoda Blueball",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
        "product_price":17999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR001001",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp",
        "new" : true,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : true
    },
    {
        "product_id":2,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Boba Fett Fighter",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
        "product_price":17999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR001002",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":3,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Luke Skywalker y Grogu",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
        "product_price":23999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR001003",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp",
        "new" : true,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":4,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"StormTrooper Lightsaber",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
        "product_price":19999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR001004",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp",
        "new" : true,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":5,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Charmander Smiley",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
        "product_price":18999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM001001",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":6,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Dragonite !Hi",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
        "product_price":21999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM001002",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":7,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Pidgeotto Flying",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
        "product_price":16999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM001003",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp",
        "new" : true,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":8,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Pikachu Smiley",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
        "product_price":20999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM001004",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":9,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Vulpix Fancy",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
        "product_price":22999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM001005",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":10,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Harry Potter & Hegwid",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "product_price":23999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT001001",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":11,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Herminione Ball Dress",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "product_price":17999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT001002",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":12,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Luna Lovegood Lion Mask",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "product_price":17999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT001003",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":13,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name":"Snape Patronus",
        "product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "product_price":15999.99,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT001004",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": true,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },

    {
        "product_id":14,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Harry Potter - Red",
        "product_description":"Remera Harry Potter - Red - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":12500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT002001",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/remera_harryPotter.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/remera_harryPotter.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": true,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
   
    {
        "product_id":15,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Hogwarts - Black",
        "product_description":"Remera Hogwarts - Black - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":14500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT002002",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/remera_hogwarts.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/remera_hogwarts.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },

    {
        "product_id":16,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Pikachu",
        "product_description":"Remera Pikachu - Gris - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":14500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM002001",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/remera_pikachu.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/remera_pikachu.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },

    {
        "product_id":17,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Pokemon Ghost",
        "product_description":"Remera Pokemon Ghost Type - Black - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":19000.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM002002",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/remera_pokemon.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/remera_pokemon.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":18,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Dark Lord",
        "product_description":"Remera Dark Lord - Black - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":20000.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR002001",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/remera_darklord.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/remera_darklord.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":19,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Remeras",
        "product_name":"Skywalker",
        "product_description":"Remera Skywalker - Black - Manga cortas",
        "product_price":16000.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR002002",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/remera_starWars.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/remera_starWars.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":20,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Darth Vader",
        "product_description":"Llavero Darth Vader - goma",
        "product_price":8500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR003001",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/llavero_DarthVader.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/llavero_DarthVader.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": true,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : true
    },
    {
        "product_id":21,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Star Wars",
        "product_description":"Llavero Star Wars - goma",
        "product_price":13500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR003002",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/llavero_StarWars.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/llavero_StarWars.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":22,
        "licence_name":"Star Wars",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Star Wars - Varios",
        "product_description":"Llavero Star Wars - Varios - goma",
        "product_price":11600.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"STR003003",
        "img_front":"/img/star-wars/llavero_StarWarsVarios.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/star-wars/llavero_StarWarsVarios.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":23,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Harry Potter",
        "product_description":"Llavero Harry Potter - plastico",
        "product_price":9800.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT003001",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/llavero_harryPotter.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/llavero_harryPotter.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": true,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":24,
        "licence_name":"Harry Potter",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Harry Potter SET",
        "product_description":"Llavero Potter - SET - Metal",
        "product_price":15300.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"HPT003002",
        "img_front":"/img/harry-potter/llavero_harryPotterSet.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/harry-potter/llavero_harryPotterSet.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },

    {
        "product_id":25,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Pokebola",
        "product_description":"Llavero Pokebola - plastico",
        "product_price":14500.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM003001",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/llavero_pokebola.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/llavero_pokebola.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : true,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":26,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Charmander",
        "product_description":"Llavero Charmander - plastico",
        "product_price":12000.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM003002",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/llavero_charmander.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/llavero_charmander.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : false
    },
    {
        "product_id":27,
        "licence_name":"Pokemon",
        "category_name":"Llaveros",
        "product_name":"Pikachu",
        "product_description":"Llavero Pikachu - plastico",
        "product_price":15000.00,
        "dues":10,
        "product_sku":"PKM003003",
        "img_front":"/img/pokemon/llavero_pikachu.webp",
        "img_back":"/img/pokemon/llavero_pikachu.webp",
        "new" : false,
        "sale": false,
        "special_edition" : false,
        "favorite" : true
    }
   


]